（约翰・C・德普二世诉 安柏点劳拉点赫德案审理历时六周）
（从2022年4月开始）
（德普和赫德间隔两周出庭作证）
（为便于理解 两场庭审的录像被剪辑在一起）
（这是他们的证词 第一次被并排展示）
约翰尼！
Johnny!
你连海湾都出不了
You'll never make it out of the bay.
孩子
Son,
我是杰克・斯派洛船长
I'm Captain Jack Sparrow.
明白？
Savvy?
他是好莱坞最大最成功的明星之一
He's one of Hollywood's biggest and most successful stars.
演员约翰尼・德普和安柏・赫德
Actors Johnny Depp and Amber Heard.
约翰尼！安柏！
Johnny! Johnny and Amber!
-约翰尼！ -安柏！
- Johnny! - Amber!
在距离好莱坞的 浮华和魅力几百公里的地方
Hundreds of miles away from the glitz and glamour of Hollywood...
约翰尼・德普 对其前妻安柏・赫德的诽谤案审判
Johnny Depp's defamation trial against his ex-wife, Amber Heard,
即将在北弗吉尼亚州开始
is set to start in northern Virginia.
以防你看肥皂剧太入迷
Just in case you've gotten lost in the soap opera,
约翰尼・德普声称安柏・赫德诽谤他 索赔5000万美元
50 million dollar claim by Johnny Depp that Amber Heard defamed him.
2018年 她在《华盛顿邮报》上写了一篇评论
She wrote a 2018 op-ed in The Washington Post
指出自己是代表家庭暴力的公众人物
referring to herself as a public figure representing domestic abuse.
德普和他的法律团队 声称赫德完全是撒谎
Depp and his legal team say that Heard is outright lying,
而且那些谎言毁了他的事业
and that those lies have devastated his career.
赫德反诉要求赔偿一亿美元
Heard countersued for 100 million in damages,
声称该演员的法律团队
alleging the actor's legal team
试图通过称她的主张为骗局来诽谤她
tried to defame her by calling her claims a hoax.
德普和赫德都不曾 在弗吉尼亚州生活或工作过
Neither Depp nor Heard live or work here in Virginia,
但因为《华盛顿邮报》 在这里有服务器和打印机
but because The Washington Post has servers here and a printer here in Virginia,
费尔法克斯县的居民将决定他们
Fairfax County residents are gonna decide their fate
在这个5000万美元案件中的命运
in this 50 million dollar case.
《德普 vs 赫德： 好莱坞夫妻诽谤案》
剧名：《第一集：真相审判》
（2022年4月 弗吉尼亚）
好了
All right,
各位
everybody.
我正在前往
Right now, I am on my way
费尔法克斯县法院
to the Fairfax County Courthouse
去排队
to get into line.
（达斯新闻）
约翰尼・德普庭审的第一天
] Day one of the Johnny Depp trial.
会有100名观众
There's gonna be 100 spectators,
包括媒体、市民、支持者和粉丝
and it's gonna be a mix of media and just civilians, you know, supporters, fans.
约翰尼・德普！
Johnny Depp!
耶！
Yeah!
我听说是先到先得 所以我得早点去
I hear it's first come, first serve. So gotta be there bright and early.
我得拿出这个抱枕
Oh, wait, I gotta take a picture of the cushion.
完美
Perfect.
好的 我要拿了
Oh, okay, I'm going for it.
爱你们 传下去吧
I love you guys. Pass it along.
把镜头翻过来 这样你们就能看到
Let's flip it up so you guys can see.
-早上好 -早上好
- Good morning. - Good morning.
排队的大家感觉如何？
How are we feeling, line?
耶
Yay.
你们知道该怎么做
You know what to do.
带话题“尊重队伍”
Hashtag "respect for the line."
“为排队正名”
"Justice for the line."
如果你是官方媒体 就必须在街那边
Okay, so if you're, like, official media, you have to be on that side of the street, right?
如果你只是粉丝 你可以来这里
If you're, like, just a fan, you can be over here.
所以我可以更近距离地看约翰尼
So I can kind of get, like, a closer look at Johnny.
约翰尼・德普起诉他的前妻
Johnny Depp is suing his ex-wife,
安柏・赫德 赔偿5000万美元损失
Amber Heard, for 50 million dollars in damages,
他诉称遭到她诽谤
claiming she defamed him.
欢迎回来 作为一线演员 约翰尼・德普和其前妻安柏・赫德
Welcome back. We're getting a closer look into the lives of Hollywood's elites
诽谤案的一部分
as part of the defamation lawsuit
我们要进一步了解好莱坞精英的生活
between A-lister Johnny Depp and ex-wife Amber Heard.
（安德鲁・蒂姆伯特 ABC新闻主播）
2020年 德普在与一家 英国小报的诉讼中败诉
In 2020, Depp lost a lawsuit against a British tabloid
该小报称他“殴打妻子”
that labeled him a, quote, "wife-beater."
他和赫德都要在 这次审判中出庭作证
He and Heard are both expected to testify at this trial.
很多人都在谈论这场庭审 有很多直播
Lots of people are talking about this, I know there's lots of livestreams happening.
你可以自己看庭审并形成自己的意见
You can go watch the trial yourself, make your own opinions of it.
网上都有 去YouTube看就行
It's online. You can go to YouTube right now and watch.
约翰尼 我们爱你！
Johnny, we love you!
今天的节目比较特别
Today is a different kind of show
因为我们要观看 约翰尼・德普对安柏・赫德案
because we are going to be watching the opening statements
的开庭陈述
in the Johnny Depp-Amber Heard case
并边观看边评述
and going through them with commentary.
好了 我拿到了旁观通行证 太棒了
All right, so I got my spectator pass. That is awesome.
（达斯新闻 YouTube博主）
（约翰C德普）
好了 我们上了五楼
Okay, so we are up here on the fifth floor.
他的庭审将在这里开始
That's where his trial's taking place.
我们不能用手机 我不应该在这里录像
Not supposed to be on our phones. Definitely not supposed to be recording up here.
这里没有安柏・赫德的粉丝
There's no Amber Heard fans.
只有约翰尼・德普的粉丝
It's only... It's only Johnny Depp fans.
这里没人支持安柏
Nobody's there for Amber.
你们还好吗？
What's up, guys?
欢迎来到法律解释 我希望你们准备好了
Welcome to Lawsplaining, and I hope you are ready.
（播放量 评论）
这是首批进入庭审的备受瞩目的
This is one of the first high-profile "Me Too" defamation cases
“我也是”诽谤案之一
that's making it into a courtroom.
这是大新闻
That is huge news.
（雷吉塔法律）
嘿 来了 这就是主角本人 约翰尼D
Hey, there we are. There's the man himself, Johnny D.
那条领带不错 我喜欢那条领带
That's a nice tie! I like that tie.
准备好迎接陪审团了吗？
- Ready for the jury? - Yes, Your Honor.
-是的 法官大人 -很好
Okay, great.
法院电视台和其他电视台 为什么能被允许转播庭审呢？
So how is it that Court TV and other stations
are even allowed to broadcast this trial?
为什么我们能像这样 进入费尔法克斯县法院？
Why do we have such crazy access into the Fairfax County Courthouse?
在弗吉尼亚州 这件事的决定权完全在于法官
In Virginia, that decision is solely up to the judge,
该案的法官签署了一项指令 允许摄像机转播
and the judge in this case signed an order permitting a pool camera to broadcast the trial.
（佩妮・阿兹卡瑞特法官 费尔法克斯县巡回法院）
女士们 先生们
Ladies and gentlemen,
我们将明确你们作为本案陪审员的责任
we're gonna go over the responsibilities you have as jurors, okay, in this case.
你们不能在任何 社交网站上阅读、观看或收听
All right, so you're not to read, watch, or listen to anything about this case
与本案相关的任何信息
on any social networking sites.
你们得到的信息
What you learn about this case
仅限于在这个法庭内得知的全部信息 好吗？
is limited to what you learn in the four walls of this courtroom. Okay?
开庭陈述？
Are we ready with opening statements?
法官在要求德普的律师做开庭陈述
The judge is asking for Johnny Depp's attorney's opening statement.
我要切换成全屏
Uh, I'm gonna cut to a full screen,
但如果有停顿的话 我会进行评述
but I will chime in with some commentary if there are some breaks.
我们开始了 来自弗吉尼亚的爆米花星球的直播
But here we go, live, uh, on Popcorned Planet here in Virginia.
-早上好 -早
- Good morning. - Morning.
这是一起诽谤案
This is a defamation case.
这个案件是关于 当虚假言辞被公开说出时
It's a case about how devastating words can be
其破坏性可以有多么巨大
when they are false and uttered publicly.
近30年来
For nearly 30 years,
德普先生被誉为
Mr. Depp built a reputation
好莱坞最有才华的男演员之一
as one of the most talented actors in Hollywood.
如今 他的名字与一个谎言关联
Today, his name is associated with a lie
由他前妻撒出的谎言
uttered by his former wife,
也就是被告 安柏・赫德
the defendant, Amber Heard,
具体而言 是她在2018年12月
specifically the words that she used
公开发表在《华盛顿邮报》上的言辞
published in The Washington Post in December 2018.
“两年前
Quote, "Two years ago,
我成为了代表家庭暴力的公众人物
I became a public figure representing domestic abuse."
我有一个难得的有利条件
"I had the rare vantage point
可以实时看到 机构如何保护被指控虐待的男性”
of seeing in real time how institutions protect men accused of abuse."
赫德小姐没有在评论中引用德普先生的名字
Ms. Heard did not use Mr. Depp's name in the op-ed.
她不必引用
She didn't have to.
两年前
Two years earlier,
赫德小姐公开指责约翰尼・德普家庭暴力
Ms. Heard had publicly accused Johnny Depp of domestic abuse.
（2016年5月 洛杉矶）
安柏 是约翰尼造成的你脸上的淤青吗？
Amber, did Johnny give you that bruise on your face?
约翰尼・德普跟女演员安柏・赫德
Johnny Depp accused of domestic abuse
突然分手 被指控有家庭暴力行为
in his sudden split from actress Amber Heard.
约翰尼有没有对你施暴？
Did Johnny brutalize you?
随着“我也是”运动的兴起
In the wake of the Me Too movement,
安柏・赫德彻底改变了 德普先生的生活和声誉
Amber Heard forever changed Mr. Depp's life and reputation.
这次庭审是为了洗清德普先生的名誉
This trial is about clearing Mr. Depp's name
让其免受可怕的虚假指控
of a terrible and false allegation.
好了
All right.
谢谢
Thank you.
罗腾伯恩先生
Mr. Rottenborn.
-我可以上前吗？ -可以 先生
- May I approach? - Yes, sir.
-大家早上好 -早上好
- Good morning, everyone. - Morning.
德普先生的团队 会试图把这个案子变成一部肥皂剧
Mr. Depp's team is gonna try to turn this case into a soap opera.
为什么？我不太确定
Why? I'm not really sure,
因为证据对德普先生很不利
because the evidence isn't pretty for Mr. Depp.
很不利
It's not.
你们会看到约翰尼・德普的真面目
You're gonna see who the real Johnny Depp is,
在名声和海盗装束的背后
behind the fame, behind the pirate costume.
一个将自己的暴力面
The man who has described himself,
描述为“怪物”的男人
the violent side of himself, as "the monster."
“怪物”
"The monster."
《华盛顿邮报》没有出现在这个法庭的被告席上
You don't see The Washington Post sitting here as a defendant in this courtroom.
他只起诉了安柏
He only sued Amber.
他本来可以起诉《华盛顿邮报》 文章是他们发表的 但他没有这么做
He could've sued The Washington Post, they published the article, but he didn't.
他选择让安柏出席在弗吉尼亚的庭审
And he chose to bring Amber to court here in Virginia,
她在这里孤立无援
where she has no ties,
她没有在这里生活过 他也没有 他们俩都没有在这里待过
has never lived, he's never lived, where they never spent any time,
因为他想毁了她的人生
because he wanted to ruin her life,
纠缠她
to haunt her,
摧毁她的事业
to wreck her career.
重点不在于 德普会把本案变成的肥皂剧
It's not about the soap opera that Depp will turn this case into.
不在于你更喜欢谁
It's not about who you like better.
甚至不在于你是否同意她写出的东西
It's not even about whether you agree with the words that she wrote.
重点在于她说那些话的权利
It's about her right to speak them.
（赫德：我大声疾呼反对性暴力）
（直面了我们文化的愤怒 这种情况必须改变）
（抖音）
德普有一支最优秀的法律团队
Johnny Depp has one of the most brilliant legal teams,
如果你需要证据 我可以给你一个词 “弗吉尼亚”
and if you need proof of that, I've got a word for you, "Virginia."
为什么两个来自加利福尼亚的名人
Why would two celebrities from California
争论《华盛顿邮报》上发表的东西
arguing about something written in The Washington Post
会在弗吉尼亚州立案？
file a case in Virginia?
在美国 诽谤法因州而异
In the USA, defamation laws vary state by state,
而弗吉尼亚州有最好的诽谤法
and Virginia has some of the best defamation laws for a matter like this.
所以我们意见一致 这不是离婚案
Just so we're all on the same page, this is not a divorce case.
这不是家庭暴力案
This is not a domestic violence case.
我认为这是伪装成诽谤案的公关活动
I would argue it's a PR campaign disguised as a defamation case.
我觉得约翰尼的目的不是打赢官司
I don't think Johnny's intention is to win the case here.
我觉得他的目的是洗清他的名声 控制自己的声誉
I think his intention is to clear his name and to control his reputation.
没有任何公关活动有机会
There is no PR campaign that has a chance
产生像这次庭审一样大的影响
of making an impact as powerful as this trial.
（布莱恩・卡伦 喜剧演员和演员 PDB播客嘉宾）
是德普想让摄像机进法庭
Depp was the one who wanted the cameras in the courtroom.
她不想要
She didn't.
你的第一个证人
Your first witness.
我们想请劳拉安柏・赫德出庭作证
Your Honor, we'd like to call Laura Amber Heard to the stand.
好的
All right.
能说出你的名字吗？
Will you please state your name?
好的 我是安柏・劳拉・希德
Yes, it's Amber Laura Heard.
好
Okay.
请问你为什么来这里？
Now, why are you here?
我来是因为我的前夫 因为我写的文章起诉我
I am here because my ex-husband is suing me, uh, for an op-ed I wrote.
你对此有何感受？
And how do you feel about that?
我很难找到词汇
I, um...I s... struggle to have the words.
我很难找到描述这件事有多痛苦的词
I struggle to find the words to describe how, uh, painful this is.
这太可怕了
Um, this is horrible.
好 请说吧 女士？
Okay, all right. Yes, ma'am?
下午好 德普先生
Good afternoon, Mr. Depp.
下午好
Good afternoon.
你能告诉陪审团 你今天为什么来这里吗？
Can you please tell the jury why you're here today?
好的
Um, yes.
大约六年前
About six years ago,
赫德小姐提出了一些 针对我的令人发指的指控
Ms. Heard made some quite heinous accusations against me
那些指控没有任何形式的事实依据
that, uh...that were not based in any species of truth.
那张臭名昭著的《人物》杂志封面
The infamous People Magazine cover with Ms. Heard
赫德小姐脸上有深色淤青
with a... a dark bruise on her face.
从来没有发生过这种事
Nothing of the kind had ever happened.
虽然我们有一些…
Though there were...
争论
arguments.
（法庭证据 录音）
-这可没用 你这个傻逼！ -你太幼稚了
-成熟点吧 -给我闭嘴
先听我说 然后你可以回应
明白吗？
但我从来没有
But never did I, myself, r... reach the point
到对赫德小姐动手的地步
of, um, striking Ms. Heard in any way,
我也从来没有攻击过任何女人
nor have I ever struck, um, any woman.
对不起
I'm sorry.
我没发现这里有人 我以为它只是浮着
I didn't realize anyone was there, I thought it was just... floating.
它的确只是浮着
It is just floating.
天啊
Oh, God.
为什么她要出现？
Why did she have to happen?
明明之前没有她 我也过得很好
Just when I was doing so good without her.
请为陪审团描述一下 你试镜《朗姆酒日记》
Please describe for the jury your experience in auditioning
时候的经历
for The Rum Diary.
我参加了几次试镜 这在我的工作中很常见
Well, I auditioned a few times, which is common in my work,
然后我接到一个电话 说约翰尼想亲自见我一面
and then I got a call saying that Johnny wanted to meet me in person.
我以为我可能是去试镜的
I thought I would be going for maybe an audition.
只是开会而已
Um... But it was just a meeting.
我去他办公室跟他见了几个小时
I went to his office, um, and... and met with him for a few hours.
她来了我办公室
She came to my office.
我看了一眼 心想
I took one look at her and I thought,
“是的 就是她了”
"Yep, that's the one."
那是我第一次见赫德小姐
That's when I first met Ms. Heard.
我们聊了书、音乐和诗
We talked about books and music, poetry.
我们有很多相同的爱好
Um, we like a lot of the same...We liked a lot of the same stuff.
我很惊讶有一个人…
I was so surprised that somebody...
我是一个无名小演员 我当时应该22岁
You know, I'm a no-name actor. I was 22, I think.
他年龄是我的两倍 而且他是闻名于世的演员
And he was twice my age and he's this world-famous actor,
而我们都喜欢老的布鲁斯音乐
and here we are getting along about......old blues,
我当时认为这很不寻常 很了不起
and I thought it was unusual and remarkable.
我离开的时候感觉：“哇哦”
I left there just feeling like, "Wow."
我记得有场戏是我在淋浴
I remember there was a scene where I was taking a shower
然后她走进房间
and then she comes into the room
她走过来 打开淋浴间 然后我们接吻
and she walks, opens the shower, and we kiss.
那让我产生了不该产生的感觉
It felt like something that I shouldn't be feeling.
在工作过程中 你要做出一些能彰显专业性的行为
There are certain things that you do in the job to, um, be professional,
比如当你演那种类型的戏时
like when you have to do that sort of scene,
要尽量避免使用你的舌头
and you don't, like... you......you don't use your tongue if you can't... if you can avoid it.
为了保持边界感 有些事是不能做的
There's certain things that you do to just maintain a certain line,
但我觉得那条边界被模糊了
and it just felt like those lines were blurred.
他抓住我的头 把我拉过去 真的亲吻了我
I mean, he grabbed my face and pulled me into him and really kissed me.
他用舌头了吗？
Did he use his tongue?
是的
Yes.
那天下班后
That day after work,
赫德小姐来到了我的拖车
Ms. Heard, uh, had come to my trailer.
他开玩笑地把我推倒在他拖车里的
He kind of playfully kind of pushed me down on this, like, bed-sofa,
沙发床上 像开玩笑一样
uh, that was in his trailer, just playful,
有些调戏意味 然后他说：“真美味”
um, and flirtatious, and he said, uh, "Yum."
遇到安柏・赫德这样的演员 她像是另一个时代的人
Meeting an actress like Amber Heard, she's of another era, you know.
这就像走进一个房间 见到维罗妮卡・雷克或贝蒂・戴维斯
I mean, it's like walking into a room and meeting Veronica Lake or Bette Davis,
或者是劳伦・巴考尔
or, you know, Lauren Bacall.
我管她叫“苗条”
I called her "Slim."
我叫她“苗条” 她叫我“史蒂夫”
I called her "Slim" and she called me "Steve."
你觉得你要怎么做？
What do you think you're gonna do?
我要拿到那个钱包 苗条
I'm gonna get that wallet, Slim.
你知道的 史蒂夫 我对你不能完全放心
You know, Steve, I wouldn't put it past you.
我的天亨弗莱・鲍嘉和劳伦・巴考尔
My God, when Humphrey Bogart and Lauren Bacall,
他们就是在那部电影里认识的 他45岁 而她19岁
that's when they met, on that film, he was 45 years old and she was 19.
你为什么那么做？
What'd you do that for?
-我一直在想我是否会喜欢 -你的决定为何？
- Been wondering whether I'd like it. - What's the decision?
我还不知道
I don't know yet.
他们一直在一起 直到鲍嘉去世
They stayed together until Bogart passed away.
我承认 我是年色已衰的鲍嘉
So, I acknowledge the... the fact that I was the old, craggy Bogey,
而她是一个尤物
and she was this... beautiful creature,
美得惊人的尤物
just this stunning creature.
那是个美丽的场合 美丽的时间
It was a beautiful place, a beautiful time,
而我爱这个男人爱得无法自拔
and, uh, I fell head over heels in love with this man.
她仿佛是一个完美的伴侣
She seemed to be the perfect partner.
知书达理 甜美 幽默
Literate, sweet, funny.
她当时棒极了
She was, uh... She was wonderful.
我们的爱非常浓烈 你知道吗？
There wasn't any love like that, you know?
我是说
I mean...
然后他会消失
And then, uh... he would...disappear.
（达斯新闻）
大家好 欢迎收看达斯新闻
Hello everybody, welcome to Darthn3ws.
这是第一天的回顾
This is gonna be a day one recap.
我在法庭里 坐在那里看现场直播
I was in the courtroom, I was sitting there live, in person.
我会给你们分享我的第一手感受
So I'm just gonna give you my first-hand account.
我不是法律学者 我不是律师 我这么做只是为了好玩
I'm not a legal scholar, I'm not a lawyer. I do this for fun.
但我有利益相关
But I have, like, a dog in the fight
因为我还真的很在乎约翰尼・德普
because I actually give a fuck about Johnny Depp.
还有男人的权利
And men's rights.
安柏！
Amber! Amber! Amber!
约翰尼！
Johnny! Johnny! Johnny!
你能描述一下 你和德普先生的关系吗？
Can you describe your relationship with Mr. Depp?
你记得他第一次打你的时候吗？
Do you remember the first time that he physically hit you?
-记得 -请跟陪审团讲述一下
- Yes. - Please tell the jury about it.
我永远不会忘记
I will never forget it.
我的人生被改变了
It changed my life.
我当时坐在沙发上
I... I was sitting on the couch,
我询问他胳膊上的纹身的事情
and I ask him about the tattoo he has on his arm.
我不知道那个纹身什么意思
I didn't know what it said,
看起来好像模糊了 褪色的纹身很难看懂
it just looked like muddled, faded tattoo that was hard to read.
那个纹身
Well, the... the, um...what it, uh... a tattoo,
写的内容是“永远的薇诺娜”
which used to say "Winona Forever,"
那是他的前女友 薇诺娜・莱德
who was a former girlfriend, Winona Ryder,
我们分手的时候
and, uh, when we broke up,
我把最后两个字母拿掉了 然后它变成“永远的酒鬼”
I took off the last two letters and had it say "Wino Forever."
我没看到
I didn't see that.
我以为他在开玩笑
I thought he was joking
因为完全看不出来 纹的是那几个字 我笑了
because it didn't look like it said that at all, and I laughed,
然后他一巴掌扇到我脸上
and he slapped me across the face.
我盯着他 然后还在笑
I just stared at him, kind of l-laughing still,
以为他也会开始笑 然后告诉我那是一个玩笑
thinking that he was gonna start laughing too, to tell me it was a joke,
但他没有
but he didn't.
他说：“你觉得好笑吗？ 你觉得这很好笑吗 贱人？
He said, "You think it's so funny? You think it's funny, bitch?"
你觉得你是有趣的贱人？” 然后他又打了我一巴掌
"You think you're a funny bitch?" And he slapped me again.
很用力
Hard.
我坐在那里 看着肮脏的地毯
I was just sitting there looking at the dirty carpet,
好奇自己为什么 以前没注意到地毯那么脏
wondering why I never noticed that the carpet was so filthy before.
我当时不知道自己还能做或说什么
and I just didn't know what else to do, I didn't know what to say,
我不知道如何反应 因为我想： “天啊 他刚才是打我了吗？”
I didn't know how to react because, "God, did he just hit me?"
德普先生 你对此有何回应？
Mr. Depp, what is your response to that?
那…
It...
那件事没有发生
It didn't... It... It didn't happen.
我从没打过赫德小姐
I have never struck Ms. Heard.
我希望我能坐在这里说 我当时站起来走出了那栋房子
I wish I could sit here and say I stood up, and I walked out of that house
我守住了底线 维护了自己
and I drew a line and I stood up for myself.
但我只是看着肮脏的地毯 试图让自己站起来
I was just looking at the...dirty carpet, trying to will myself to get up.
我当时心碎了
I was...heartbroken.
她在演戏
She's acting.
她在撒谎
She's lying.
你能说出你的名字以供记录吗？
Will you please state your name for the record?
惠特尼・亨利奎兹
Whitney Henriquez.
-你是安柏的妹妹？ -我是
- And you're Amber's sister? - I am.
请形容你和德普先生早期的关系
Describe your relationship with Mr. Depp in the early stages.
我们一开始相处得很好
We got along really well at first. Um, he was sober at the time,
他当时没有酗酒 清醒状态的约翰尼
and Johnny, when he's sober,
是非常聪明漂亮、和善可爱的
is very bright and beautiful and lovely and kind and generous,
他也非常平易近人
and he was very easy to get to know.
坦白说 我们一开始都爱上他了
And frankly, we all fell in love with him at first.
但是很快
But, very quickly,
随着他们的关系进展 形成了一种模式
this pattern emerged, uh, as their relationship went on
那就是 如果约翰尼在吸毒或者喝酒
that if Johnny was using or if he was drinking,
他们就总是会吵架
there was almost always a fight.
约翰尼清醒的时候 非常可爱 有魔力 很幽默
Johnny, when sober, was lovely and magical and very funny.
可卡因和任何酒精
Cocaine and any kind of alcohol...
会带出他非常丑陋的一面
...would bring out a very, very ugly side of him.
非常厌女和残忍
Um, very misogynistic and cruel.
他在喝酒
He was almost unrecognizable
和滥用药物的时候 跟平时判若两人
when he was drinking and using to an excess.
他会变得非常生气
He would just get very angry,
他会说一些关于她的很可怕的话
and he would just say really horrible things about her.
他会编造一些精心设计的情景
He would weave these elaborate situations
在那些情景中 安柏与她合作过的每一个男人
in which Amber was having affairs with every man that she ever worked with
以及接触过的每个女人都有染
and every woman she ever came in contact with.
他变得非常卑鄙
He... He became very demeaning.
“她毫无才华
You know, "She has no talent,
当她的奶子开始下垂 脸开始长皱纹的时候
and when her tits start to sag and her face gets wrinkly,
没有人会再对她有兴趣”
nobody is gonna be interested in her."
他说她是“用烂了的垃圾袋”
He called her "a fucking used-up trash bag," uh,
“谄媚的婊子”“下垂的婊子”
"slimy whore," "saggy whore."
“该死的贱逼” 他说过很多这种话
You know, "fucking cunt" was thrown out a bunch.
这些可怕的形容
Um, just horrible things like that.
（2016年2月 洛杉矶 约翰尼・德普的豪宅）
（法庭证据 安柏・赫德的电话录像）
婊子养的！
Motherfucker!
怎么了？
What happened?
今天早上什么都没发生 你知道吗？我只说了对不起
Nothing happened this morning, you know that? All I did was say sorry.
你今天早上发生什么事了吗？
Did something happen to you......this morning?
我不这么认为
I don't think so.
不 就是这样
Um... No. That's the thing.
你想看我发疯？那我就他妈疯给你看
You wanna see crazy? I'll give you fucking crazy.
这才是疯
Here's crazy.
你疯了 你疯了吗？
All your crazy. Are you crazy?
你今早把这个全喝完了？
Have you drunk this whole thing this morning?
你开始了吗？
Oh, you got this going? You got this going?
-不 我才刚开始 -哦 真的吗？
- No, I just started it. - Oh, really?
-是的 -真的吗？
- Yes. - Really?
她试图在他不知情的情况下录像
So she's trying to record him without him even knowing that.
你为什么要录像 安柏？
Why did you videotape this, Amber?
问得好
Yeah, good question.
因为我知道他不会记得
'Cause I knew he...wouldn't remember.
-他会否认 -反对 推测原因
-  He'd deny it. - Objection. Calls for speculation.
反对有效
Sustained.
当有人在你面前 怒气冲冲地破坏某件东西时
When somebody breaks something in anger in your presence,
这就是法律意义上的虐待行为
that is legally an act of abuse.
而他…看看他
And he is... he's... Look at him.
他在踢东西 摔东西 破坏东西
I mean, he's kicking stuff, he's slamming stuff, he's breaking stuff.
她在想：“嘿 这是怎么回事？”
She's like, "Hey what's going on?"
我知道这时候他没有打她 但他在做非常有攻击性的事情
And, here, I know he wasn't hitting her, but he was doing some very aggressive things,
而且就在她的面前
and directly in her presence.
如果她过来说： “我们之间有过这段对峙
And if she's coming in and saying, like, "Well, hey, here's this confrontation that happened."
我被吓到了 我觉得这是虐待行为”
"I was intimidated by it. I felt this was an act of abuse,"
她可以给出她的观点： “我身处在虐待性的关系之中”
then she can give her opinion, that "I was in an abusive relationship."
我不是企图为她辩护或怎样
I'm not, you know, trying to defend her or say it,
我的意思是 这对他来说是个大问题
but I'm just saying, you know, it's... it's a huge problem for him.
-早上好 德普先生 -早上好 罗腾伯恩先生
- Morning, Mr. Depp. - Morning, Mr. Rottenborn.
这件事我们谈过一点
Mr. Depp, we've talked about this, uh, a little bit,
但你作证表示 虐待可以有很多种形式 是吗？
but you've testified that abuse can come in many forms, correct?
身体虐待是其中之一？
Physical being one of them?
-没错 -口头是吗？
- Indeed. - Verbal?
没错
Indeed.
精神虐待？
Psychological abuse?
没错
Indeed.
你也同意 你在那段视频里很暴力 对吧？
And you would agree that you were violent in that clip, correct?
显然我当时过得不好
Clearly, I was having a bad time.
我觉得最有趣的是她试图偷偷拍摄
I thought what... what was most interesting is that she tried to hide it from me,
然后到了最后她开始笑
and then that she laughed and smiled at the end.
我个人认为那一段是最有意思的
I thought that was the most interesting part myself.
所以...是的
But... So, yes.
-你没有反应… -我的确攻击了一些柜子
- You didn't react... - I did assault, um, a couple of cabinets.
但我没有碰赫德小姐
But I did not touch Ms. Heard.
-而且… -你应该能看到吧 不是吗？
- And... - As you can see, I think. No?
你在那段视频里可能喝醉了？
You may have been drunk in that video, correct?
有这种可能性
There's a possibility of that. Yes, sir.
你给自己倒了一巨杯红酒对吧？
You... You... You poured yourself a, um, a megapint of red wine, correct?
巨杯？
A megapint?
是的
Yeah.
我给自己倒了很大一杯红酒
I poured myself a large glass of wine.
-对 -我觉得那很有必要
- Right. - I thought it necessary.
等等
Wait for it.
你给自己倒了一巨杯红酒对吧？
巨杯？
A megapint?
我给自己倒了很大一杯红酒
I poured myself a large glass of wine.
（社交媒体上的部分人 称本・罗腾伯恩）
（创造了“巨杯”这个词）
（但是英国庭审的笔录）
巨杯？
A megapint?
对约翰尼・德普 进行交叉盘问的律师说
The lawyer conducting Johnny Depp's cross-examination said,
“我们看到你倒了…”
"We saw you pour a sort of..."
约翰尼・德普说：“一巨杯”
Johnny Depp says, "A megapint."
律师说：“一巨杯红酒
The lawyer says, "A megapint of red wine,
不是每个人 都会选这个当早餐 是吧？”
which is not everybody's choice for breakfast, is it?"
巨杯
Megapint, megapint, megapint...
再来一杯
巨杯
Megapint, megapint...
巨杯？
A megapint?
那是安柏
That's Amber.
（丹尼・塞瓦洛斯 NBC法律分析员 播客嘉宾）
她只需要证明他虐待了她
All she needs to prove is that he abused her. I say "all,"
但她要么是撒谎 要么是被虐待过
but either she's making everything up, or there's been abuse.
不只是社交媒体
It's not only social media,
但当他的越野车停在法院门口时
but when his SUV pulls up at court,
不管安柏・赫德说什么
no matter what Amber Heard alleges,
外面都有一群 看到约翰尼・德普就无比兴奋的人
there's a crowd out there who are just gobsmacked by Johnny Depp.
约翰尼！
Johnny, Johnny, Johnny!
记住 我们都没在场
Remember, none of us were there.
（利莫尔律师 法律评论员 爱与秩序播客主播）
对我们来说是“我们相信谁？” 但永远都不要忘记 我们不在场
With us, it's, "Who do we believe?" But never, ever forget, we were not there.
早上好 德普先生
Good morning, Mr. Depp.
早上好
Good morning.
德普先生 现在我想谈谈2016年4月
Mr. Depp, I'd like to discuss April 2016 now.
看看这颗宝石 位于洛杉矶市中心的历史核心
We'll take a look at this gem in the historic core of downtown LA.
（德斯蒙・肖 CBS新闻记者 来自CBS新闻音频 看看这！）
这是东哥伦比亚大楼
This is the Eastern Columbia building,
洛杉矶市中心最负盛名的地方之一
one of the most prestigious places to live in downtown Los Angeles.
This art deco gem at the corner of Broadway and Ninth.
德普在这里拥有五套顶层公寓
Johnny Depp owned five penthouses here.
（2009年3月 德普赫德相识 2015年2月 婚礼）
我的生日快到了 我们计划在我们的顶层公寓共进晚餐
My birthday was coming up, and we had a dinner planned at our penthouse.
他在那天的某个时刻告诉我
He, uh, told me at some point that day
他安排了一个商务会议 或者金钱会议 他好像是这么说的
that he had scheduled a business meeting, or a... "a money meeting," I think he said, maybe.
我迟到了1小时40分钟 差不多
I was about an hour and 40 minutes late, maybe, something like that.
德普先生 当你到达派对时 赫德小姐 是否跟你打了招呼 怎么打的？
Mr. Depp, when you arrived at the party, how did Ms. Heard greet you, if at all?
非常冷漠
Very cold.
德普先生在你的生日迟到了 这对你来说是件大事 不是吗？
It was a big deal to you that Mr. Depp was late to your birthday dinner, wasn't it?
是的 我觉得是件大事
Yeah, it... Yeah, it did matter to me.
-你不高兴他迟到了 -是的 我当时很受伤
-And you were upset he was late. -I was. I was hurt.
她在我们的卧室门口对我摆脸色
She squared off at me in the doorway of our bedroom.
我记得他堵在门口
I... I remember him blocking the door,
不让我出去 推搡我
blocking me to get out, kind of shoving me down,
我们有口头争吵 然后开始互相推搡
and, well, we had a... a... you know, a verbal argument, and then that became a shoving match.
我试着推回去
I tried to shove him back.
我说：“来呀 打我”
And I said, "Go ahead, hit me."
嘭
Bam.
然后我就说：“这是你想要的吗？
And then I just said, "Is that what you wanted?"
你还想再打一下吗？”
"Would you like another?"
嘭
Bam.
她打了第二下
There's the second one.
然后我说：“很好 你打完了”
And I said, "Good, now you're done."
抓住她的肩膀
Grabbed her by the shoulders,
送她上床
walked her to the bed,
让她坐下 并说
sat her down, and said,
“别跟着我
"Don't follow me."
别管我
"Leave me alone."
我离开了 我走了”
"I'm out. I'm gone."
约翰尼把我摔到床上
Johnny wrestled me down on the bed.
我记得我起来过一两次 最后还是倒回床上了
I remember I got up once or twice before I ended up on the bed,
然后他抓住了我
and he grabbed me. Um...
他做了他嘲讽我时 会做的一件事 他抓住我的…
He did this thing that he did sometimes when he would taunt me, he'd grab me by the...
耻骨
um, the pubic... bone,
把我压下去 按住耻骨 然后把我拉过去
just pushed me down, held me down by it, and kind of pulled me into it,
他还在嘲讽我 问我是不是觉得自己很强硬
and, um, was kind of taunting me, asking me if I thought I was so fucking tough.
“你觉得你是个硬汉吗？ 看看谁这么强硬
"You think you're such a fucking tough guy, huh?""Are you so tough now? Look who's so tough.
你想当男人吗？”
You wanna be a man?"
我去拿了几样东西
I went, I grabbed a few things,
然后我马上离开了
and I got out immediately,
我去了另外一处房子
and I went to, um...my other house.
但他说：“我们结束了 我们在离婚 都结束了”
But he's saying, "We're fucking done. We're divorcing. This is over."
然后在4月22日的凌晨4点30分
And then at 4:30 a.m. on April 22nd,
那是安柏的生日 他离开了安柏
which is Amber's birthday, he left Amber.
是的 他在安柏的生日上 “永远地离开了她”
Yes, he leaves Amber, like, "for good," quote unquote, on her birthday.
真是野蛮
What a savage.
我的朋友们 这就是职场的男权
My friends, this is the patriarchy at work.
赫德被称作婊子 拜金女 疯婆娘
Heard's being called a whore, a gold digger, a crazy bitch,
控制欲强 怪物
manipulative, a monster.
（贱人）
（他看起来好紧张）
他的罪行得到了同情和宽恕
He is being given empathy and forgiveness for his transgressions
但赫德无法获得
in a way Heard is not.
这是典型的怪罪受害者 这就是为什么大家不报告虐待行为
It's victim-blaming at its finest. This is why people don't report abuse.
目前为止 在这段故事里 你相信谁？
So far, who do you believe in this story here?
其实他们两个我都相信 他们在证人席上 都宣过誓
- I kinda believe both of 'em. Um... - Okay. They're on the stand, they're under oath.
他们不可以撒谎 如果他们撒谎被发现 可就麻烦了
- Yeah. - They're not allowed to lie. If they get caught in a lie, it's big trouble.
说到公开 这就是娱乐圈 不是吗？
In terms of it being public, well, that's, uh... that's showbiz, isn't it?
生日晚餐后的第二天
After your birthday,
你和你的朋友们在科切拉音乐节庆祝
you and your friends went to Coachella to celebrate your birthday.
-对吗？ -对
- Is that correct?  - That is correct.
-这段视频里 你在开车 -对
- You're featured in that video driving. - That's correct.
我去找到我的一个安保团队 说：“她去科切拉了
I had gone to one of my security team and said, uh, "She's in Coachella."
我觉得现在是去市中心 拿些东西的好时机”
"I think it's a good time to go downtown so that I can get some of my things." You know?
他说：“我觉得现在不适合去”
And he said, "I don't think now's a good time to go."
我想：“现在是最佳时机 她两天内都不会回家”
And I thought, "It's the perfect time. She's not gonna be home for two days."
然后他给我看了他手机里的一张照片
And then he showed me a photograph on his telephone.
什么照片？
What was the photograph of, Mr. Depp?
粑粑 说吧 粑粑！
Poop. Say it. Poop!
那是…
It was a... It was a...
那是一张床的照片
It was a photograph of the bed,
在我睡的那一侧
and on my side of the bed...
是人类的粪便
was human fecal matter.
他知道这有多愚蠢
He knows how fucking stupid it is.
我对此的第一反应是
My initial response to that,
真的有人可以拉一坨…
that some human being had actually dropped a, uh...
“便便”到床上
..."grumpy" onto the bed...
这太奇怪了
It was so bizarre...
太荒谬了
and so grotesque...
我只能笑
...that I could only laugh.
请你举起你的右手
If you'd raise your right hand for me.
你是否在法律的约束下 发誓或确认说实话？
Do you swear or affirm to tell the truth under penalty of law?
-是的 -谢谢
- I do. - All right. Thank you, sir.
你认识本案原告约翰尼・德普吗？
Mr. Jenkins, do you know the plaintiff in this case, Johnny Depp?
是的 我认识
Yes, I do.
你也跟赫德小姐一起去科切拉了吗？
Were you also going to Coachella with Ms. Heard?
是的 安柏和她的朋友们在科切拉时
Yes, I was. I was the transportation for Amber and her friends
是我负责接送
while she was at Coachella.
当你那天晚上送赫德小姐
And did you have any discussions with Ms. Heard
去科切拉的路上 你们有没有任何交谈？
on the way to Coachella that evening?
我们聊了她在离开公寓前
We had a conversation pertaining to the surprise she left
留在老板床上的惊喜
in the boss's bed prior to leaving the apartment.
赫德小姐对于 德普先生床上的粪便有何说辞？
And what did Ms. Heard say about the defecation in Mr. Depp's bed?
是一个失控的恶作剧
A horrible practical joke gone wrong.
你有没有搞恶作剧？
Did you commit any kind of prank?
绝对没有
Absolutely not.
首先 我不觉得那很好笑
First of all, I... that... I don't think that's funny.
就是这样 那太恶心了
Period. That's disgusting.
她还想把责任推到狗身上
Uh, and she tr-tried to blame it on the dogs.
小布上厕所有什么问题吗？
What, if any, issues did Boo have...Oh, they're disparaging the dog!...with bathroom problems, if you will?
约翰尼当时的狗 小布
Johnny's dog, uh, at... at the time, Boo,
她在还是小狗的时候 吃了约翰尼的大麻
she had eaten Johnny's weed when she was a puppy
一直都控制不住大便
and had, uh, bowel control issues.
你为什么不觉得可能是狗拉的？
Why didn't you think it could've been the dogs?
他们是茶杯约克夏
They're Teacup Yorkies.
每一只重约3.6斤
They weigh about four pounds each.
很明显
It was clear.
那不是狗拉的
That did not come from a dog.
（你好 我是安柏大便）
（大便）
（大便党）
这可能是他第一次
That's probably one of the first times that he really realized
真正意识到她有多疯狂
the depths of how fucking insane that she was.
（她没有在床上拉屎 约翰尼在英国庭审中承认
小布曾吞食他的大麻 经常控制不住大便）
请记录德普发过这则短信
It was shared on the record that Depp sent this text,
“你能不能蹲在主卧前
quote, "Will you squat in front of the door of the master bedroom
拉一大坨便便 这样安柏踩到的时候
and leave a giant coil of dookie so that Amber steps in it
会想是其中一只狗 尤其是小布 有了大毛病？
and thinks that one of the dogs, primarily Boo, has a major problem?"
那多有趣”
"It'll be funny."
在2014年10月29日
On the 29th of October 2014,
赫德小姐给凯文墨菲发了一则消息
Ms. Heard wrote in a text message to Kevin Murphy
说“昨晚 小布在约翰尼睡觉时 拉在他身上了
that, quote, "Last night, she," as in Boo, "shit on Johnny while he was sleeping,
他满身都是 毫不夸张”
like all over him, not exaggerating."
再次 这是公开记录
Again, public record.
（2016年5月 安柏・赫德生日后一个月）
德普先生 你为什么 在2016年5月21日去顶层公寓？
Mr. Depp, why did you go over to the penthouses on May 21st, 2016?
赫德小姐要求我过去聊聊
Ms. Heard had requested, uh, that I come over to... to have a talk.
所以我带着我的安保团队去了
I... I went over there with my security team,
杰瑞・嘉吉和肖恩・贝特
Jerry Judge and Sean Bett,
以免事态失控
just in case anything went down.
-早上好 贝特先生 -早上好
- Good morning, Mr. Bett. - Good morning.
你的屏幕上能看到吗 贝特先生？
Do you see this on your screen, uh, Mr. Bett?
能看到
I do.
穿黑色和白色衬衫的是你吗？
That's you in that black and white shirt, right?
那是我
That's me.
戴帽子的是德普先生 他的左边是嘉吉先生
That's Mr. Depp in the hat, and that's Mr. Judge to his left.
是的
Correct.
这段视频拍摄的是
And this video is when you're entering
你进入东哥伦比亚大楼 带他去三号顶层公寓的时候 是吗？
the Eastern Columbia building to take him to Penthouse Three, correct?
没错
That's correct.
约翰尼和我快一个月没见了
Johnny and I had not seen each other for the better part of a month.
我看得出来他烂醉如泥 但很平静
I mean, I could tell he was inebriated, but it was peaceful.
然后他又开始说大便的事情
And then he starts talking about the feces again,
他说是我的一个朋友恶作剧
and this prank that he said one of my friends had left for him
在我床上给他留下了那些
in my bed.
我眼睁睁看着我们的婚姻崩溃
Our marriage was falling apart in front of our eyes,
我们一个月没见
we hadn't seen each other for a month,
我不敢相信他想谈论的是大便
and I couldn't believe he wanted to talk about feces.
所以我给一个朋友打了电话 觉得能彻底解决这件事
So I call this friend, thinking that will take care of it.
-我说… -告诉我们那个人是谁
- And I say... - Tell us who that person is.
艾欧
Io.
她让我用免提通话
She put me on speakerphone.
她说：“约翰尼觉得你和我一起
She said, "Johnny thinks that you and I together
在他的枕头上大便”
defecated on his pillow."
所以我开始笑
So I started laughing,
他觉得很不安 因为我和她觉得这件事很可笑
and he got very agitated by the fact that she and I thought it was funny.
当我意识到他是认真的
And when I realized that he was serious,
我就说：“好吧 听着 首先
I was like, "Okay, look. You know, first of all,
我那天不在那里”
I wasn't there that day."
这让约翰尼更生气了
It just made Johnny madder.
他更不爽了 抓起了手机
He got more upset, grabbed the phone,
开始大声咒骂
and started screaming expletives,
一些侮辱性的词汇
insulting names.
我对艾欧说：“你可以拥有她了
And I said to Io, "You can have her now."
她是你的了 完全是你的了” 是吗？
"She's yours. She's all yours." Right?
他把手机扔到沙发上 然后上楼了
He tosses the... the phone, you know, down on the couch and heads upstairs,
我捡起手机
and I pick up the phone.
艾欧说：“安柏 立即离开那栋房子
Io said, "Amber, get out of the house. Get out of the house now."
你不安全”
"You're not safe."
约翰尼从楼梯上冲下来
Johnny came bolting down the stairs,
从我手上抢过手机
grabbed the phone from my hand,
拿着手机往后摆手臂
just pulls his arm back with the phone,
然后把手机扔到了我脸上
and throws it at my face.
打到了我的…感觉是眼睛上
Hit me right in my... It felt like my... my eye.
我当时站在冰箱边
I was by the refrigerator at this point.
我大概有6米远
I was 20 feet away.
-赫德小姐当时在哪里？ -还坐在沙发上
- Where was Ms. Heard at that time? - She was still sitting on the couch.
在我哭的时候 他走过来
He comes over to me, um, as I'm crying.
他说：“是的 我打到你了 是吗？
He says, "Oh yeah, I hit you, huh?"
不如我把你的头发往后拽？”
"What if I pull your hair back? What if I pull your hair back?"
他对她说：“哦 你以为我打了你？
He said to her, "Oh, you think I hit you?"
你觉得我他妈打了你？
"You think I fucking hit you?"
不如我把你该死的头发扯下来？”
"What if I peel your fucking hair back?"
然后我听到手机又掉了 然后我听到她的尖叫
And then I heard the phone drop again and then I heard her scream.
她还在跟艾欧通话
She's still got Io on the phone,
她就是在那个时候开始尖叫的
and that's when the screaming started.
“别打我了 约翰尼” 她尖叫道
"Stop hitting me, Johnny," she's screaming.
她用尽全力
In... In her best, uh,
她吓坏了 用非常难受的声音尖叫
freaked out, upset voice, high-pitched.
我们能听到赫德小姐的尖叫和大喊
We could hear the screaming and shouting from Ms. Heard,
所以我马上打开了门
so I immediately opened up the door,
嘉吉先生和我跑了进去
and Mr. Judge and I ran in there.
接下来我听到的是“老板”
Next thing I hear is, "Boss, boss!"
然后我意识到 他的两个保安进入了公寓
And I realize that his two security guards had come into the... to the apartment.
她脸上带着惊讶
She had this look of surprise on her face,
然后她看着德普先生和我们 然后大声叫道
and then she looked at Mr. Depp and us, and she shouted out loud,
“这是你最后一次对我做这种事”
um, "This is the last time you do this to me."
“这是你最后一次打我
"That's the last time you'll ever hit me."
这是你最后一次对我做这种事”
"That's the last time you'll ever do that to me."
再说一次 我在6米开外的冰箱边
And again, I'm a good 20 feet away, by the fridge.
当时德普先生看着她说
At which point, Mr. Depp looked at her and said,
“你在说什么鬼东西？”
"What the hell are you talking about?"
我记得她尖叫着
I remember her screaming...
然后我挂掉电话打了911
and I hung up the phone and I called 911.
警官们好 你们还好吗？
Hello, officers. How you doing?
请让我们进门
Want to just come in and just check.
我们需要确保 里面的所有人都没事 然后我们…
We need to make sure everybody in here is okay and then we...
你为什么不愿意配合警察？
Why didn't you want to cooperate with the police?
因为我想保护约翰尼
Because I... I...I wanted to protect Johnny.
我不想让他被逮捕
I didn't want him to be arrested.
谁是安柏？
Who's Amber?
约翰尼绝对不在这里
Johnny is definitely not here.
-他不在这里？ -不在 先生
- He's not here? - No, sir.
那一切都好吗？
Everything's all good then?
-现在很好 是的 -好的
- Now it is, yes. - All right.
谢谢
Thank you.
我最好的朋友拍了我的照片
My best friend took pictures of me.
这是电话事件后我的脸
This is my face after the phone incident.
你能清楚看到赫德小姐吗？
Did you have a clear view of Ms. Heard?
我可以
I did.
-你能清楚看到她的脸吗？ -我可以
- Did you have a clear view of her face? - I did.
你有没有看到赫德脸上的任何伤痕？
Did you observe any injuries on Ms. Heard's face?
没有
None.
（2016年5月 洛杉矶）
（六天后）
约翰尼・德普即将离婚的妻子
Johnny Depp's soon-to-be ex-wife has received
已收到针对这位电影明星的 家庭暴力限制令
a domestic violence restraining order against the movie star.
安柏・赫德在法庭上展示了这张照片
Amber Heard presented this photograph in court
作为指控家庭暴力的证据
as evidence of the alleged domestic violence.
嘿 安柏
Hey, Amber.
安柏 是约翰尼 造成的你脸上的淤青吗？
Amber, did Johnny give you that bruise on your face?
-安柏 -约翰尼打你了吗？
- Did Johnny beat you up? - Amber, what...
我看到她去了法庭
I saw that she had gone to a court
当时到处都是狗仔 她和…
and there were paparazzi everywhere, and her and a,
脸上有一块棕色痕迹
um, brown mark on her face.
在这之前
Had you ever been
你是否曾被指控对女人有身体虐待？
accused of physically abusing a woman before this point?
没有
No.
宝贝 你没有被拳打
别告诉被拳打是什么感觉
你打过很多架 你已经出道很久了 我知道
-当你握紧拳头… -你没有被拳打 你是被打了
抱歉我打了你 但我没有拳打你
我没有对你重拳出击
我他妈是在打你
我不知道我的手具体是什么动作
但你没事
我没有伤害你 我没有拳打你 我是在打你
我没有坐在这里抱怨吧？是你在这样
这就是我和你的区别 你很他妈幼稚
-因为是你挑起的 -你太幼稚了！
Because you started it.
-成熟点吧！ -因为是你开始动手的
-的确是我开始动手的 -是你 我必须出来
是的 你做得对 你太成熟了…
你知道吗？你很值得敬佩
她在录音里承认打了约翰尼・德普
The fact that she's on tape admitting to hitting Johnny Depp,
（尼克・维尔 电视嘉宾 维尔档案播客主播）
而她还为 《华盛顿邮报》写了这篇评论
for her to have written this op-ed for The Washington Post
而且将自己推举为 “我也是”运动中的代表人物
and essentially propped herself up as a figurehead in the "Me Too" movement.
-是的 -可以这么说
- Right. - So to speak.
你会有种被背叛的感觉
Yeah, it... it... I think you... you just feel really betrayed.
这对很多人来说都难以接受
It's so triggering to so many people.
作为家庭暴力的受害者和幸存者
As a victim and a survivor of domestic violence,
虽然这是性别歧视 但你一般都会想支持女性
even though it's sexist, you do want to kind of back the female,
但到目前为止 我觉得她更像是侵犯者
but so far, I feel like she was more the aggressor.
他们可能都不占理 安柏可能很糟糕 你可以相信这一点
Look, they can both be wrong. Amber can be awful. You can totally believe that,
（乔丹・克里滕登 播客主播 黑暗世界播客音频）
但我们不能以此为理由 为约翰尼・德普
but we can't use that as a reason for Johnny Depp to be absolved
开脱他所做的那些可怕的事情
of the clearly awful things that he has done.
好了
All right. Cross-examination.
交叉盘问
交叉盘问 开始了
Cross-examination. Here we go.
-下午好 赫德小姐 -下午好
- Good afternoon, Ms. Heard. - Good afternoon.
一开始很尊重
Starting out respectful.
德普先生在整个庭审过程中 都没看过你一眼 对吧？
Mr. Depp hasn't looked at you once this entire trial, has he?
是的 他没有
Ooh! No, he has not.
我没看到 是的
Not that I've noticed, no.
你知道德普先生 为什么不回头看你吧？
You know exactly why Mr. Depp won't look back at you, don't you?
我知道
I do.
你和德普先生最后的会面
One of the last times you ever saw Mr. Depp
是你们2016年7月在旧金山见面
was when you met in San Francisco in July of 2016,
这是在你获得
and this is after you had obtained
针对他的家庭暴力限制令之后
the domestic violence restraining order against him.
没错
That's correct.
哦 直接开始放音频
Oh, right into audio.
不要 一个拥抱解决所有问题 这一切 我们一起经历过的那么多事
我只是想触碰你
-在你说过那些屁话之后？ -我想给你一个拥抱
在你指控我做过那些事之后 你想触碰我？
-是的 请停下 -你他妈疯了
求你了 我只是想拥抱你
-不 我们再也不会见彼此了 -求你了
- Please. - You won't even...
你都不愿意…别他妈摘我的眼镜
你不会再看到我的眼睛了
那是你和德普先生的录音
That's you and Mr. Depp in that recording.
是的
That is.
他信守了诺言 对吧？
And he kept that promise, hasn't he?
据我所知 他不能看着我
As far as I know, he cannot look at me.
“他不能”
"He cannot."
-他不愿看着你 是吧 赫德小姐？ -他不能
- He won't look at you, right, Ms. Heard? - He can't.
让我们播放原告的357A号证物 该证物已经是证据了 法官大人
Let's please play plaintiff exhibit 357A, which is already in evidence, Your Honor.
看看陪审团和法官怎么想
告诉全世界 约翰尼
告诉他们 约翰尼・德普
“我 约翰尼・德普
-我也是家庭暴力的受害者” -是的
这是公平的战斗
看看有多少人相信或支持你
-录音里是你的声音？ -是的
- That's your voice on that recording? - Yes, it is.
你认为他不会公开承认 自己是家庭暴力的受害者？
You didn't think he would tell the world he was a victim of domestic violence, did you?
我觉得他这样做会很疯狂 因为我知道我们经历了什么
I thought it would be crazy for him to do so knowing what I know we lived through.
你的回应是什么？ 在你听到赫德小姐说
What did you say in response when Ms. Heard said,
“告诉全世界 约翰尼
"Tell the world, Johnny."
告诉他们 约翰尼・德普 我也是家庭暴力的受害者”
"Tell them, 'Johnny Depp, I'm a victim too of domestic violence'"?
我说：“是的 我就是”
I said, "Yes. I am."
赫德小姐
Ms. Heard,
德普先生是你的受害者 不是吗？
Mr. Depp is your victim, isn't he?
不是 女士
No, ma'am.
在他离开你之后
And once he left you,
你公开称他为虐待者 这是你继续虐待他的方式 不是吗？
you continued to abuse him publicly by calling him an abuser, didn't you?
他是个虐待者
Uh, he is an abuser,
你可以在网上查我们两个人 看谁才是被网络暴力的那个人
and you can look either of us up online and figure out who's being abused online.
（傻婊子）
（安柏・赫德去死）
（贱逼）
安柏大便！
Amber turd! Amber turd! Amber turd! Amber turd!
这是一场舆论战
This is a battle of optics.
重点不是法律依据 而是公众的看法
This is not so much about the legal merits but rather what the public perception is.
（德拉拉・格尔吉安 内容创造者 维尔档案播客嘉宾）
如果你只看公众意见
If you just look at public opinion,
没有人真的相信安柏・赫德
no one really believes Amber Heard.
我一点都不买账…你相信吗？
I don't buy it for a... Do you buy this?
抖音“为约翰尼・德普讨公道”的话题 有超过40亿的浏览量
The hashtag "Justice for Johnny Depp"
has more than four billion views on TikTok.
互联网已经做出了决定
It seems the Internet has made up its mind
而这场庭审都还没有结束
without this court case even coming to a close.
（约翰尼第一视角）
你的回应是什么？ 在你听到赫德小姐说
“告诉全世界 约翰尼
告诉他们 约翰尼・德普
我约翰尼・德普 一个男人
我也是家庭暴力的受害者”
我说：“是的 我就是”
是的 安柏完蛋了
Yeah, Amber's fucked.
字幕翻译：Zeo Niu